iwearyourshirt.com 2019-07-13

# Wandering Aimfully Privacy Policy – Wandering Aimfully

* * *

###### PRIVACY STATEMENT

We are committed to protecting your privacy. Only authorized inviduals within the company have access to any information collected from individual customers. We constantly review our systems and data to ensure the best possible service to our customers.

Email signups on this website are collected via Drip; their privacy statement and terms can be found at [https://www.drip.co/privacy](http://convertkit.com/privacy) This website is hosted, built, and managed on the WordPress platform. Payments on this website are processed via Stripe (their privacy statement and terms can be found at [stripe.com/us/terms)](http://stripe.com/us/terms) as well as PayPal (their privacy statement and terms can be found at <https://www.paypal.com/us/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full>.)

* * *

###### INFORMATION COLLECTION, USE, AND SHARING

We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.

You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time.

You can do the following at any time by contacting us via [hello@wanderingaimfully.com](mailto:hello@wanderingaimfully.com):

  * See what data we have about you, if any.
  * Change/correct any data we have about you.
  * Have us delete any data we have about you.
  * Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
